[
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 33-42?",
    "choice1": "75",
    "choice2": "-9",
    "choice3": "-23",
    "choice4": "17",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 40-33?",
    "choice1": "12",
    "choice2": "11",
    "choice3": "7",
    "choice4": "3",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 17-24?",
    "choice1": "7",
    "choice2": "41",
    "choice3": "-41",
    "choice4": "-7",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -137+30?",
    "choice1": "-107",
    "choice2": "167",
    "choice3": "-93",
    "choice4": "-150",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -40+63?",
    "choice1": "103",
    "choice2": "31",
    "choice3": "-93",
    "choice4": "23",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -87+93?",
    "choice1": "8",
    "choice2": "6",
    "choice3": "-11",
    "choice4": "13",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 57-13?",
    "choice1": "36",
    "choice2": "19",
    "choice3": "44",
    "choice4": "27",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -37+45?",
    "choice1": "15",
    "choice2": "7",
    "choice3": "21",
    "choice4": "8",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 54-17?",
    "choice1": "37",
    "choice2": "24",
    "choice3": "41",
    "choice4": "13",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es 233-254?",
    "choice1": "312",
    "choice2": "43",
    "choice3": "7",
    "choice4": "21",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es +40 x -30?",
    "choice1": "70",
    "choice2": "-1200",
    "choice3": "-700",
    "choice4": "900",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -13 x -12?",
    "choice1": "130",
    "choice2": "-120",
    "choice3": "156",
    "choice4": "24",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es +31 x +11?",
    "choice1": "42",
    "choice2": "310",
    "choice3": "-110",
    "choice4": "341",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -13 x +7?",
    "choice1": "-91",
    "choice2": "21",
    "choice3": "-24",
    "choice4": "70",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -12 x -9?",
    "choice1": "109",
    "choice2": "108",
    "choice3": "-97",
    "choice4": "-21",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -7 x -9?",
    "choice1": "+13",
    "choice2": "-16",
    "choice3": "63",
    "choice4": "24",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -14 x +15?",
    "choice1": "-29",
    "choice2": "19",
    "choice3": "-203",
    "choice4": "-210",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es +12 x -7?",
    "choice1": "-84",
    "choice2": "19",
    "choice3": "-19",
    "choice4": "48",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es +14 x +9?",
    "choice1": "23",
    "choice2": "126",
    "choice3": "-47",
    "choice4": "140",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuánto es -16 x -12?",
    "choice1": "-31",
    "choice2": "-43",
    "choice3": "192",
    "choice4": "43",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
